<Document>
#NANOTRASEN OFFICIAL NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT: SECTOR APPALIA MAJORIS
##COMMAND TRAINING MANUAL

	[bold]Do not speak about the contents of this document in public. Report whistleblowers to the Nanotrasen Representative for contract termination.[/bold]

	Greetings, esteemed department head. There are a variety of workplace hazards that can be encountered on the station. This document aims to shine some light on some of them.

	If you are the head of a civilian department you should focus on the survival of your team and allow Security to do their job.

##POSSIBLE THREATS:

- The Syndicate

The Syndicate remains the primary threat to security, and their presence should be expected on station in one form or another.
The Syndicate has definite plans to steal critical station infrastructure and kill station personnel, among other designs.
Despite this, the average agent is not an extreme threat, and will attempt to achieve their goals undetected.

- Nuclear Operatives

Nuclear Operatives are still at large, performing strikes on stations in the sector. If the station is being attacked by "Nukies", everyone in the crew should immediately arm up to prevent the nuke from going off.
The captain should [bold]not[/bold] be fighting them at the front lines.

- The Spider Clan

A secretive organization known as the spider clan has been detected in the sector. Their operatives can be identified by their green katanas and their stealth suits. Should a member of command spot one, immediately report them to security. Their intentions in the sector are unknown.

- Changelings

Changelings have historically appeared on stations, eating crewmembers and taking their skin.
Their presence is detectable by hollowed corpses or by their signature mutations. Hard evidence of changelings warrants arming of security personnel, ideally with incendiary munitions.
That said, there haven't been any changeling sightings in years.

- Hostile Xenofauna

Xenomorphs, Space Dragons, and other wild beasts can rapidly infest stations.
Address them with full force.

- Romerol

Zombies are exceedingly rare but very real. Command should attempt to group up with security or reinforce their department against the threat.

- Chimera

Letoferol is a powerful romerol based bioweapon concocted by the Syndicate, it mutates people into highly intelligent and hostile Chimeras. Stay around Security.

- Bingles

Bingles are a small threat if caught early, but can still overwhelm stations. Stay away and allow security to handle them.

- Abductors

Grey Aliens seemingly perform random abductions on crew, but cause minimal harm. They are near impossible to capture due to their teleportation technology, stay close to your team to prevent abductions.

- Revolutions

Revolutions are an existential threat to crew loyalty and to corporate decorum. On any signs of a revolution, attempts should be made to locate the ringleaders, and they should be executed promptly.
[bold]Disloyalty is never tolerated.[/bold]

- Blobs

Blobs infestations should warrant the arming of any and all available crew to prevent TOTAL STATION LOSS.

##ARCANE THREATS:

- Wizards

Members of the Wizards Federation are highly dangerous, command should avoid them at all costs.

- Heretics

Heretics are lunatics who have ignored the above demands of the SOP and have begun research into the forbidden.
They are to be considered threats of the highest caliber, and should be [color=#ff0000]executed on sight[/color]. Consider their capabilities unknown, but dangerous.

- Cults

Should you spot any cult like activities, immediately distance yourself and report it to security.

- Ghosts

Ghosts and spirits are the purview of the chaplain, and should be left to them.

- Demons

Demonic Entities Cannot be reasoned with, and should be handled with lethals only.

- Shadowlings

Shadowlings can corrupt the minds of crew members. If they become strong enough your mindshield will not save you. Report them to security so they can be exterminated.

- Devils

The Devil is real but impossible to contain. Leave hunting him to the chaplain. Making deals with the devil is illegal and crew members who attempt to do so should be reported to Security.
Confirmation of the existence of the devil does NOT mean Santa or the IRS are real.
</Document>