<Document>
#NANOTRASEN OFFICIAL
##POTENTIAL THREAT ASSESSMENT: SECTOR APPALIA MAJORIS

	Welcome back, Officer. As is standard for your return to shift, this is your briefing on emergent threats to the station. 
	
	[bold]Do not share the contents of this document with non security or command personnel.[/bold]

THE CHANCE OF ANY THREAT APPEARING ON STATION IS LOW, BUT NEVER ZERO.

	ON AVERAGE, A STATION UNDERGOES AN INCIDENT INVOLVING OUTSIDE POWERS ONCE PER THREE MONTHS. STAY VIGILANT.

##POSSIBLE THREATS:

- The Syndicate

The Syndicate remains the primary threat to security, and their presence should be expected on station in one form or another.
The Syndicate has definite plans to steal critical station infrastructure and kill station personnel, among other designs.
Despite this, the average agent is not an extreme threat, and will attempt to achieve their goals undetected.

- Nuclear Operatives

Nuclear Operatives are still at large, performing strikes on stations in the sector. If the station is being attacked by "Nukies", everyone in the crew should immediately arm up to prevent the nuke from going off.

- The Spider Clan

A secretive organization known as the spider clan has been detected in the sector. Their operatives can be identified by their green katanas and their stealth suits. They are highly lethal and should be executed or captured as fast as possible. Their intentions in the sector are unknown.

- Changelings

Changelings have historically appeared on stations, eating crewmembers and taking their skin.
Their presence is detectable by hollowed corpses or by their signature mutations. Hard evidence of changelings warrants arming of security personnel, ideally with incendiary munitions.
That said, there haven't been any changeling sightings in years.

- Hostile Xenofauna

Xenomorphs, Space Dragons, and other wild beasts can rapidly infest stations.
Address them with full force.

- Romerol

Zombies are exceedingly rare but very real. Defend the medbay at all costs while they produce Ambuzol. Engaging in close quarters will almost certainly result in your death.

- Chimera

Letoferol is a powerful romerol based bioweapon concocted by the Syndicate, it mutates people into highly intelligent and hostile Chimeras. Similar to romerol, defending the medbay while they make the cure is the best option.

- Bingles

Bingles are a small threat if caught early, but can still overwhelm stations. Treat them as lesser Xenomorphs.

- Abductors

Grey Aliens seemingly perform random abductions on crew, but cause minimal harm. They are near impossible to capture due to their teleportation technology, defend the crew from them using lethal force.

- Revolutions

Revolutions are an existential threat to crew loyalty and to corporate decorum. On any signs of a revolution, attempts should be made to locate the ringleaders, and they should be executed promptly. Disloyalty is never tolerated.

- Blobs

Blobs infestations should warrant the arming of any and all available crew to prevent TOTAL STATION LOSS.

##ARCANE THREATS:

- Wizards

If a member of the Wizards Federation is spotted on station, security should immediately gear up to execute them. [color=#ff0000]TAKE ZERO RISK[/color]. Do not stop until the threat is confirmed to be dealt with.

- Heretics

Heretics are lunatics who have ignored the above demands of the SOP and have begun research into the forbidden.
They are to be considered threats of the highest caliber, and should be [color=#ff0000]executed on sight[/color]. Consider their capabilities unknown, but dangerous.

- Cults

Cultists are typically the product of brainwashing. Minimal force should be used unless the cult is overtly hostile. Work with the chaplain to deconvert cultists.

- Ghosts

Ghosts and spirits are the purview of the chaplain, and should be left to them.

- Demons

Demonic Entities Cannot be reasoned with, and should be handled with lethals only.

- Shadowlings

Shadowlings can corrupt the minds of crew members. If they become strong enough your mindshield will not save you. Execute them on sight.

- Devils

The Devil is real but impossible to contain. Leave hunting him to the chaplain. Making deals with the devil is illegal and crew members who attempt to do so should be arrested.
Confirmation of the existence of the devil does NOT mean Santa or the IRS are real.
</Document>
